撒旦
Satan,
魔鬼
the Devil,
惡魔
Lucifer,
暗黑王子（魔鬼的別稱）
Prince of Darkness,
閻羅王
Yanluowang,
彼勒（魔鬼的別稱）
Belial,
亞巴頓（地獄的魔王）
Abaddon,
別西卜（魔鬼的別稱）
Beelzebub,
暗黑王子（魔鬼的別稱）
Prince of Darkness.
別西卜（魔鬼的別稱）
Beelzebub,
彼勒（魔鬼的別稱）
Belial,
亞巴頓（地獄的魔王）
Abaddon,
撒旦
Satan,
魔鬼
the Devil,
路西法
Lucifer,
別西卜（魔鬼的別稱）
Beelzebub,
彼勒（魔鬼的別稱）
Belial,
暗黑王子（魔鬼的別稱）
Prince of Darkness.
早
Good morning.
Neil!
Eh?
什麼問題？太前衛？
What? Too daring?
要是其他人，我早湊他了
Not if you're daring people to kick your ass.
這叫“炫”啊，小哥
It's called pea-cocking, bro.
女生對顏色鮮豔的特別感冒
Alright, females are attracted to bright colours.
效果如何....
How's it--
目前效果如何？
How's it working so far?
你懂的，效果顯著
You know, it's working well.
男人就該展示自身優勢！
You've got to play to your strengths.
氣派與魅力，你懂的！
Style and charm,you know what I mean.
你該大膽露兩手
You should play to yours,
你的“內內裡藏牌技”！
you should bust out those panty dropping card tricks
沒在別人前做過呢
that you never show anyone.
女生不喜歡牌技
Girls don't like card tricks.
開啥玩笑？
Are you kidding?
她們當然喜歡
Of course they do.
她們不喜
No, they don't.
她們喜歡
Yeah, they do.
小哥，雜誌《男人健康》說
Dude. According to Men's Health
女性有18%機會跟會玩牌技
females are 18 percent more likely to sleep with a guy
的男人上床
after seeing a card trick.
你造嗎？
Really?
真的
Yeah,
2010年5月，學習啦
May 2010. Look it up.
嗨，美女
Hey gorgeous.
美女，賞面看個牌技嗎？
Gorgeous, would you like to see a card trick?
可以啊
Sure.
選一張，別讓我看到
Alright, pick one and don't show me.
現在撕掉
Now tear it up.
交回給我
Can I have that back.
給他
Give it to him.
是這張嗎？
Is this your card?
不是，差太遠
No, not even close.
看一下你的胸罩
Check your bra.
說什麼？
What?
看一下你胸罩
Check your bra.
太神奇，你怎麼做到的？
That's amazing, how did you do that?
行規不能說
I can't tell you.
她回來了
She's coming back...
頂爆，真的有效
Oh my god, it's working!
下周我家有個派對
Listen, I'm having a party
at my house next weekend.
你該來走走
You should come.
太意外了
That sounds amazing,
但那天要上教堂，所以...
but I've got this church thing so...
上教堂
Church thing.
Church thing...
不是的，不是的...
No, no, no, no, no.
Neil只是發功後出現的副作用
Neil just gets exhausted after a show,
他休息一下就回復正常了
you've got to give him a break.
你發什麼神經？
What?
什麼回事，小哥，上教堂？
What the hell was that, man,church?
你本有機會搞上她的，你懂的，
You're supposed to try to get in her pants, you know,
不是改造她的信仰
not convert her.
我清楚，故意搞砸的
I know, I blew it.
至少有機會摸她咪咪
You at least touched her boob.
我沒機會
I didn't.
你怎麼“突變”了？
Well, then how did you?
“魔”法發功了
It was magic.
你現在意淫摸她咪咪嗎？
Are you magically touching a boob right now?
Denise，他對Cheryl剛打過主意來
Hey Denise, he just totally felt up Cheryl.
我知道了
Yeah, I know.
她是Kent的“對象”
And so does Kent.
他正趕赴現場，你最好保命
He's on a rampage, you'd better hide your ass.
死了，死了，快跑
Oh shit, oh shit, hurry up.
這裡
Over here.
該死
Oh fuck.
死了
Oh shit.
那個“小次貨”呢？
Where is that little shit?
呃，呃...
Uh, the, uh...
Neil!
Neil，是Neil嗎，你都認識的
Neil, yeah Neil is you know Neil.
他夠膽在我女友胸罩放牌
He put a card in my girlfriends bra,
我勢要將他撕成碎片
I'm going to tear him in half ike a phone book.
開門，否者要你嘗嘗
Open the door or I'll put you through it.
別，別開
No, no, don't.
他吉人自有天相的！
Uh, alright man just alright.
Matt, 沒義氣
Matt, fuck.
你在裡面搞什麼飛機？
What the fuck are you doing in there?
你在打飛機？
You jacking it?
同志們，Neil在儲物室打手槍
Hey everyone, Neil's jerking off in the closet,
多變態噁心的小子
what a fucking gross little perv.
噁心！
Eew!
別搞他，混蛋
Leave him alone, asshole.
滾蛋
Go.
讓他辦完
Lets let him finish.
懷春少年 PK 撒旦大王
【大奔字幕】
嚴禁用於商業用途，僅供學習交流！
週末不是用來睡懶覺嗎？
I don't know, wouldn't you rather be
sleeping in on the weekends?
這每週的一小時，能讓父母開心
It's only an hour a week and
it makes our parents happy.
他媽的討厭上教堂，假死了
I fucking hate church, so lame.
趕快，穿上教服
Come on, put your robe on.
等一等
Wait, wait.
撒旦王在上
In Nomina Satanas.
撒旦王萬歲！
Hail Satan!
Hail Satan.
撒旦王萬歲！謝主隆恩
Hail Satan, and thank you Satan.
兄弟姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
阿司塔羅斯王慶典臨近
as the celebration of Astaroth approaches
該內省我們崇拜撒旦王的緣由了
it is time to ask ourselves why do we worship Satan?
是因為他允諾賦予信徒的法力嗎？
Is it for the power he has  promised us?
是慶祝末日善惡之爭即將來臨的勝利嗎？
Is it to be on the winning side at the final battle of Armageddon?
崇拜撒旦王讓我們自由
The worship of Satan allows us to eat freely
吸收知識與善惡之樹，
from the tree of knowledge,of good and evil.
給我們在地球，天堂和地獄間
It gives us the freedom to indulge our senses
縱欲的自由
in the pleasures of Earth,Heaven and Hell.
耶穌基督
Jesus Christ.
褻瀆神明啊！
Blasphemy!
大家可以別分心嗎？
If we could have everybody's undivided attention?
感謝
Thank you.
掉鏈子了
Where was I.
說到“真理選邊站”
Side of truth.
對，兄弟姐妹們
Oh yes, brothers and sisters
崇拜撒旦王這玩意
the worship of Satan is all of these things.
其核心無非圍繞 “真理選邊站”
But most of all it is to be on the side of the truth.
為了上帝，讓不潔流出你的雙眼
是欺世盜名，撒旦才是救世主
Let the scales fall from your eyes for God is
the deceiver and Satan is the salvation.
很快我們就會進行阿司塔羅斯王慶典
Soon we will perform the celebration of Astaroth,
Neil小弟會完全奉獻自己來挫敗
our young brother Neil will give himself over completely
天堂強加給撒旦大王的罪名
to our Lord to foil the accursed forces of Heaven.
撒旦王萬歲！
Hail Satan!
呈上祭品
Bring forth the offering.
啊，是只山羊呢
Aw, look at the goat.
主，小小心意，不成敬意
Lord, please accept this humble sacrifice.
我真想代它去死
I would totally trade places with that goat right now.
作為信仰的標誌
As a token of our faith.
做看官就好
Just keep watching.
撒旦王在上！
In Nomina Satanas!
記住，週三本會有餅賣
And remember, this Wednesday we're having a bake sale
善款全數作為保齡球隊和
to raise money for our bowling team and also the star
阿司塔羅斯節慶典的香油錢
of our upcoming celebration of Astaroth ceremony,
Neil因此很努力準備
Neil, is working so hard to prepare.
我們以示支持一下
Lets show him our support.
沒錯
Oh yeah.
剛才儀式說話這事
Hey, so this talking during church thing.
很過癮，對嗎？
Pretty fun, is it?
娘，爹，聽我解釋
Mom, Dad, listen.
不必了
No, no, no, no, no.
你那不嚴肅和哄笑
I can actually see how joking and laughing
正正讓我家出醜
and embarrassing your family you know instead of
而沒考慮到要專心聽佈道
paying attention to the sermon could be a little entertaining.
是Matt鬧起的
Matt totally started it.
老是說Matt的錯，是嗎？
Okay, it's always Matt's fault huh?
真相就如此
Yes, actually it is.
你餘生就沒想過要
Are you going to go through the rest of your life
對自己行為負起責任嗎？
never taking responsibility for your actions?
是嗎？
Huh?
我有想過
Yeah.
說真的嘛
Oh really.
Sheldon老大，我們正就佈道被打斷的事
Sheldon, hi, we were just talking about how sorry we are
深表歉意
for that interruption during the sermon.
希望如此啦
I should certainly hope so.
你知道下次故事版本就不一樣了
You understand that next time it's quite a different story?
我懂的
Yes sir.
準備得怎麼樣？
How are the preparations going?
他已準備好
Oh, he's ready.
為何不說說咱教會各大王的名呢
In fact, why don't you recite for them the names of our Lord.
對，說說
Yes, do tell.
說出來
Tell us.
路西法，阿發米特，別賊蔔
Lucifer, Affamet, Beezelbub.
是“別西蔔”才對
That's Beelzebub.
別西蔔，彼勒，阿巴頓
Beelzebub, Belial, Abbadon.
有超過40個尊稱呢
There are over 40 of them  you know.
年輕人，下點功夫背背
You should take time to learn them.
慶典為你準備很精彩的東西
There are such fabulous things in store for you.
我可以走了嗎？
Can I go?
全體教友熱切期盼儀式的到來
We're all very excited for the ceremony.
同感
So am I.
會樂也融融的
Should be fun.
你沒讓他破處吧？
So, you've kept him chaste?
都是自然守身如玉的結果
Oh, that problem kind of took care of itself.
我還沒惹上過麻煩
You know, I never got into trouble
直到你家入了這教會
until your family joined this church.
你也沒好玩過
Yeah, and you never had any fun either.
是嗎？是嗎？
Did you? Did you?
別搞我
Get off me.
我還沒搞清楚
You know, I still just don't understand
這誓約的玩意
this whole oath business.
譬如，他們想快活就快活
Like, they made you lock up your dick
而卻要你不破處
while they're all getting it on.
說不過去呢，太他媽不公平
That doesn't make any sense, it's not fucking fair.
他們偷走你青春最可貴的
They're stealing the greatest part of your youth,
“春色滿園關不住”
the hot steamy sexual part.
為何你會同意呢？
Why would you agree with something like that?
我不可以上床，因為不被允許
I'm not getting laid because I'm not allowed to,
你想怎為我辯護？
what's your excuse?
我懂的
Oh, I see, I see.
你內心的恐懼，對嗎？
So, you're scared huh?
我不恐懼
I'm not scared.
不是嗎？
No, no?
你有特殊潔癖？
You've got a little case of the vagaphobia.
我沒特殊潔癖
I don't have vagaphobia.
嚴肅說，你得
Seriously though, you've just got to,
你得自己探索出這東西
you've got to figure this shit out man.
以免為時已晚
Before it's too late.
嘿，老爸
Hey Dad.
因為我們該
Because really Neil,what we should be doing
用“小弟”比試一番來看
is tripping over each others dicks to see
誰能泡到最多妹，悟到了嗎？
who can bag the most babes,you know?
儘管去“幹”
Fuck something.
任何人
Anything.
那傢伙有心病
That kids got problems.
對，有病的是你
Yeah, and that problem is you.
再見，Neil
Bye Neil!
想確定一下你們倆
We just wanted to make sure that both of you
是否準備好著這一切的到來
were spiritually prepared for what's going to happen.
當然，托撒旦鴻福
Of course, it's a great honour.
儀式很快完，對嗎？
It will all be over very quickly, right?
盡我所能吧
Oh, just as quick as I can make it my dear.
我能對你保證
I can assure you that -
會讓短劍又快又順地刺入肉身
That the dagger plunges into the flesh swiftly, smoothly.
聽起來會很痛苦
It sounds so painful.
不會太痛
No, no, no.
他會有點癢痛，但不會太久
He'll feel a little pinch but for no more than an instant.
這樣說，無痛
So, no pain.
不是，會痛的
No, there will be pain.
痛不欲生
Extreme pain.
血流成河
And blood, lots and lots of it.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
正如之前說過，這過程不僅無痛，還很暢快
As I was saying this whole process is
not only painless but euphoric.
我有個瘋狂想法
I have a crazy idea.
為何不能直接告訴他所有事呢
Why don't we just sit him down and explain everything to him,
這樣他心裡有個準備
that way he'll be prepared.
你要跟他怎麼說呢
What are you going to tell him, okay,
跟他說他好友會為他收屍？
that his best friend is going to have to
mop him up after the ceremony?
別說，Shelly
No. Shelly, come on.
他會接受的
He'll accept it.
他深愛撒旦王的
He loves Satan.
Sheldon老大，請見諒
Sheldon, I'm so sorry.
不必，拜託
No, no, please please.
不要讓小傢伙迷惑不解
There's no reason to confuse the little fellow.
來不及多想了
We don't have time for second thoughts.
如果不在他十八前黃昏，十八黎明前
If we don't perform the ritual
on the equinox of his 18th year
耶穌基督會回歸，破壞千年來的地球安寧
Jesus Christ will return and usher
in a thousand years of peace on Earth.
你願看到嗎？
Is that what you want?
不
No.
哥也不願
I didn't think so.
所以，建議你拋開疑慮
So, my advice to you is to  put your misgivings aside
一切往好的方面想
and focus on the positive.
吃蛋糕啊
Eat some cake.
對，好好享受今晚的慶典
Yeah, you should be enjoying your big night.
上面加霜淇淋嗎？
Want some ice cream on that?
當最後晚餐一樣大吃一頓
You should be eating like there's no tomorrow.
是個小丑呢，爸
It's a clown, dad.
十八歲生日啊
I'm 18.
你有什麼心事？
Why don't you tell us what's wrong?
為女而煩嗎？
Is it a girl?
不是
No.
實情是，有點
Actually, yeah kind of.
Oh.
有發生過什麼嗎？
Did something happen?
細節方面，就不想勞煩你們了
I'm not going to bore you with the details.
你看著我
You're going to look me in the eye
老實跟我說
and you're going to answer me truthfully,
有任何身體接觸不？
was there any physical contact?
沒有
No.
就是說沒性交？
So, there was no intercourse?
性...沒
Inter-- No.
口交呢？
And no oral?
卿卿我我呢？
Giving or receiving?
沒有
No.
肛交呢？
What about anal?
頂爆，媽
Jesus, mom!
答你媽，有沒肛交？
Answer your mother, was there anal?
沒有
No.
我保證，發生過的事
Okay, look, something happened that will ensure
都沒上床這檔事
I will never get laid in my whole life.
兒子，你可以跟我訴任何心事
Son, look, you know you can talk to me about anything.
我沒違反那蠢爆的誓約
I didn't break my stupid oath, alright.
那就好
Okay then.
那誓約不蠢呢，心肝寶貝
The oath isn't stupid honey,
這是你降生的主要原因
it's the whole reason you were born.
我們在你年齡，搞大了，我們
We were your age when I conceived and we just,
當時不知所措，但Sheldon跟我們說
we didn't know what to do but Sheldon told us
你的降生有特殊目的
that you had a special purpose.
我相信你正遭受
Look, I'm sure you're going through
一些讓你困惑的懷春問題
some pretty depressing teenage stuff right now.
我也這樣過，做過，甚至也剪過白癡髮型
Been there, done that, even I had a stupid haircut once
誰不是？
didn't I?
但你代表咱家和教會
But you are representing our family and our church,
當儀式結束後，你會全明白
when it is all over you will have a fuller understanding
這一切的意義
of what it is all about.
我去放水
I've got to take a leak.
Gary，我們需要跟他說
Gary, we need to tell him.
你知道他不喜歡驚喜的Σ( ° △ °|||)︴
You know how he hates surprises,
要是我們跟他解釋
if we just explain it to him.
死也不可！
Absolutely not!
他會壞場，哭場，鬧場，叫場的！
He'll cause a scene, crying and kicking and screaming.
你想別人笑話嗎？
Do you want other people to see that?
你都聽到了
Look, you heard , okay,
他已飽受夠多的屈辱了，信我
he has suffered enough humiliation, trust me.
我們沒權選擇Neil的命運
We did not choose Neil's destiny.
他自己選擇的
He did.
Lucifer, Baphomet, Belial,
Abbadon, Beelzebub, Belial,
Prince of Darkness,
Lucifer, Baphomet, Belial,
Abbadon, Beelzebub...
讓你們知道不僅是Neil
I want you to know that it won't just be Neil
從他犧牲裡獲得恩賜
who will be rewarded for his sacrifice.
為新紀元碰杯
To a new era.
感謝
Thank you.
快日落了，甜心
It's almost sundown, dear.
失陪一下？
Oh, would you kindly excuse us?
請便
Of course.
晚上好
Good evening.
Lucifer, Baphomet, Belial,
Abbadon, Beelzebub, Belial.
我因你自豪
I am so proud of you.
謝媽
Thanks.
你一向都很聽話的
You've been such a good son.
兄弟在此
There he is buddy, huh?
風雲人物
Man of the hour.
聽說你跨入成年世界一刻
Listen, I heard that after the confirmation
這廳的女人任你選的哦
you get to bone any woman you want
from within the congregation.
換作我，我會選Colette，
If it were me I'd go for Colette
讓她男友乾瞪眼
and make her boyfriend fucking watch.
別給我抹黑
Don't embarrass me.
我有過嗎？
Do I ever?
好了，各位信眾，開場了
Okay everybody, time to get started.
雞凍嗎？
Are you excited?
兄弟姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
咱們為了一古代儀式，齊聚一堂
we are gathered together for an ancient ceremony.
莊嚴又美好
Momentous and beautiful.
大會開始前，請關上你們的行動電話
Before we begin please turn off your cell phones
及相關電子設備
and all other electronic devices.
十八年前，咱們大王選了這小子
Eighteen years ago our Lord chose this young man
加入我們陣線對抗“大騙子”（耶穌）
to join him in battle against the Great Deceiver.
他的聖靈今晚會跟大王匯合
His spirit will join with the Father on this night.
現在我們請求Neil小子的
We now ask young Neil
俗世軀殼躺上我們的祭壇
to lay his earthly vessel upon our altar.
作為我們大王的僕人
Handmaidens of our Lord.
老兄
Dude.
估計他們會當著
I think they're going to fuck you
眾人的面幹你
right here in front of everyone.
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas.
現在是時候釋放他的聖靈
Now the time approaches to release his spirit
到我們大王的身邊
into the arms of our father
從此以後，他的聖靈會永世伴隨大王
whereupon his soul will join our King for all eternity.
被宰的“羔羊”會跟路西法下地獄相隨
The sacrificial lamb will stand with Lucifer in Hades.
哇，哇，被宰的羔羊？
Whoa, whoa, sacrificial lamb?
比喻而已
It's a metaphor.
一旦撕開處男的肉身
As we tear the virgins flesh asunder
鮮血一湧而出，以作祭忌聖體
so that the blood may spill forth in holy offering.
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas,
In Nomina Satanas...
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas,
老兄
Dude.
撒旦大王
Satanas Rex.
老兄
Dude!
哇哇哇，搞什麼？
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what the?
撒旦王在...
In Nomina...
搞飛機！
What the fuck!
撒旦王！
Satanas!
Neil! Neil!
嗨！
Hey!
Neil!
抓住他！
After him!
Neil!
回來
Get back here!
快跑
Go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
勒個去
Okay, holy shit.
快跑
Come on.
草
Oh fuck!!!!!!!
過來，快
Come here, quickly!
給力
Come on.
他們在嗎？
Are they there?
我另外一隻鞋呢
Where's my other shoe?
太抱歉了，Sheldon
I am so sorry, Sheldon.
不知道說什麼好
I mean, what can I say?
你啥不必說
You can say nothing!
接一下
Get that.
Hello?
日出前要搞定，否者時機就過了
We have until sunrise or the window will close.
要是失敗了，撒旦的憤怒會降臨我們頭上
If we fail his wrath will fall on us all!
不，這不會發生
No, that won't happen.
我逮他回來，馬上上祭壇
I'll go get him he'll be back on that altar in no time.
不，你留在這
No! You stay right here.
帶上這兩個，抓他回來
Take these two with you and fetch them back.
耍軟的，讓他乖乖回來
We need a soft touch to lure them back.
你懂我說啥，是嗎，Colette?
You know what I'm talking about,don't you Colette?
嗯
I think so.
聰明女，去
Good girl, now go.
記住，給平時一樣低調行事
And remember, as always to keep a low profile.
你們，要是他們回不來
And you, if they don't return
考慮開除你會籍
consider yourself excommunicated
你永遠看不到“地獄之門”
and you will never see the gates of Hell!
Matt! Matt!
你搞什麼，Matt
What the fuck are you doing, Matt!
搞飛機啊
What the fuck, man?
你不能拿
You can't take that,
那是我家暑假墨西哥旅行費
that's my families Mexico money for the summer.
我深感抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry
你去墨國Acapulco玩爽點
why don't you enjoy your lovely time in Acapulco
還有記得他們要你命前寄明信片給我
and don't forget to send me a
postcard before they murder you.
老兄，我爸也是個混蛋
Dude, look my Dad's an asshole too, okay.
同感
I know.
蠢爆
Oh fuck me.
打給員警就好
I'm calling the cops.
什麼？
What?
別這麼做
No, no, no, don't do that.
別
Don't do that.
死開
Fuck off.
別
Don't do that.
我爸是警員，半數警員入我們教會
Alright, my Dad's a cop and half
the force goes to our church.
報警
Police, please.
不，給我
No, give me.
Hello?
警察局
This is the police.
嗨，我是Matt，Paul的兒子
Hey. It's Matt, Paul's kid.
我爸變成禽獸了
My Dad's gone rogue.
Matt，你在哪？
Matt, where are you?
我在朋友Neil的家
I'm at my friend Neil's house.
Neil跟你一起嗎？
Is Neil with you?
在那別亂跑，我派人過去
Stay where you are, we'll
send somebody right now.
你派誰過來
Who are you sending?
Matt，在那別亂跑
st  stay  where  you  are  Matt.
草
Oh shit, fuck!
我們得跑
We've got to go!
遜爆，現在本可以在Cheryl家參加派對
This sucks, alright, we could be at Cheryl's party right now
好好享受陰道自助餐或嗎啡
totally enjoying the all  you can
eat vagina buffet or muffet if you will.
等一下
Wait.
這一切都是因為你是處男，
This all happened because you're a virgin right,
這樣的話，破處了，問題就解決了
so we get you laid problem solved.
我懂了
Oh, I've got it.
你打給誰
Who are you calling?
別打電話
Stop, stop, stop calling people.
為何？
Okay, what?
找Denise！
Denise!
老友愛愛，太絕了
A friend fuck, oh that's brilliant.
快。之前一直給她“騎著”
Come on, I mean we give her rides all the time I mean.
Neil!
小Matt？
Matty?
你們在嗎？
You guys here?
出來！
Come on out!
你想太多了
You're overthinking this, man.
她是我朋友，好不好
She's my friend, alright,
我不想讓她覺得被利用了
I just don't want her to feel like she's being used.
她沒被利用，她在救你狗命
She's not being used,she's saving your life.
她是在救我命
I know, she's saving my life.
千真萬確
Exactly.
這就是我跟他坦白的原因
That's why I'm just going to tell her the truth, alright.
Denise人太好，她會理解的
Denise is super cool,man, she'll totally get it.
不，你出發點很好，但女人不太肯
No, that's sweet okay but women don't really respond well
面對真相，他們喜歡神秘
to the truth okay, it's like they like mystery.
像你的魔術
It's like your magic.
要是你揭穿魔術
If you told them how you did the magic
你就失去魔力
you lose the magic, right?
問我雞巴多長
Ask me how big my dick is.
什麼
What?
為何要我問這個
Why would I ask you that?
除非我都看過
Besides, I've seen it.
腳趾這麼長
It looks like a toe.
給點耐心，問就好
Just bear with me okay, just ask.
你雞巴多長
How big is your dick.
原則上，我不喜歡張揚
Well, I don't really like to talk about it but, you know,
24cm
it's 9 and a half inches.
現在輪到我問，你雞巴多長
Okay, see, now I'll ask you, how big is your dick?
我不知道，還沒量過
I don't know, I've never measured it.
平均長度？
Average?
不對，25cm
Wrong! Ten inches.
為何要撒謊
Why would I lie?
要是撒謊了，會被拆穿的
If the lie works I'm going to get caught.
有何關係，世事就這樣
It doesn't matter that's the thing.
當她發現只有13cm
Okay, by the time she finds out that it's only five inches
都已經進去5cm
it's two inches deep.
Matt，你呆在這
Oh, okay, okay Matt you're going to stay outside, okay.
我不會當旁證的
I'm not doing this for an audience.
很好
Fine.
好的
That's fine.
我會洗手的
I wash my hands of this,
我在這打電話好了
I just I'll just be out here making phone calls.
沒去Cheryl那裡？
No Cheryl's, huh?
對她沒那個
Wasn't-- Wasn't feeling it,
可以進來嗎
um, can I come in?
當然，怎麼不可
Yeah, sure, why not.
你父母在家嗎
Are your parents home?
沒
No.
在這關卡住兩天了
I've been stuck on this level for like two days.
第三天還這樣，就鐵定心腸上網找外掛
I swear, one more day of this and I am
pillaging the internet for cheat codes.
老兄，能坐下嗎，好煩人呢
Dude, can you sit down,this is pretty annoying.
好的，我要聊一下
Okay, okay, I really need to talk.
我真需要跟你談些東西
I really need to talk to you about something.
比較大的事
It's kind of a big deal.
好的，說啊
Okay, talk.
嗯
Yeah.
只有Denise可以這麼忙！
Only Denise can be this busy!
搞啥
Okay.
嗨，Amy
Hey, Amy.
是Matt，聽我說
It's Matt, listen.
今晚有些瘋狂事發生
There's some crazy shit going down tonight
世界末日之類的狗屎
like end of the world type stuff
Cheryl的派對可能是你
so Cheryl's party might be your last chance
跟我最後道別？
to get with me, alright?
回頭見
Holler back.
你知道我多尊重你的
You know how much I respect you.
嗯
Yeah.
很尊重，嗯
So much, yeah, okay.
我覺得你很棒
Um, I think you're awesome.
我覺得你有點呆
I think you're kind of a dork.
我即將要說的
Uh, what I am about to ask
未曾跟其他人說過
I can never ask anybody else.
好的，喜劇大師
Okay, drama queen.
只想你對我說，可以為我做件事
I just need you to say that you
will do this one thing for me
我承諾以後不會再向你這樣要求
and I promise I will never ask you for anything ever again
只要我活著，可能活不長
as long as I live, which might not be for long.
說來聽聽
Lets hear it.
我要你今晚跟我做愛
I need you to have sex with me tonight.
如果你不肯，我會死
If you don't I'm going to die.
我只要放它進去
I just, I just need to put it in
不必有任何花招
it doesn't have to be anything special.
我不知道會“幹”成什麼樣子
I don't know what the fuck I'm going to be doing
我甚至連規則都不清楚，我不清楚...
but I don't even know the rules I don't know I just -
搞什麼飛機，Neil？
What the fuck, Neil?
今晚有些瘋狂事發生
There's some crazy shit going down tonight
世界末日之類的狗屎，所以Cheryl派對
like end of the world type stuff
so Cheryl's party might be
可能是我的最後道別？
your last chance to get with me so.
回頭見
Holler back.
正常來說，我不會想到跟你做任何事
Normally I would never think of doing anything
更別說是做愛
remotely sexual with you
但我真他媽太性急了
but I am really fucking desperate.
我只要你讓我幹
I just need you to just let me just fuck
沒別的意思
like just no meaning to it,
幹一下就好，成事就好
just the tip,anything will work.
繼續說，情聖，我底褲都濕了
Oh, keep going lover boy really my panties are dripping,
說真的
I swear.
他們來了
They're here!
草
Holy fuck!
噢
Oh.
Denise.
好的，我們做吧
Okay, lets do it.
真的，你這些突然髒話很吸引
Really, the sheer balls of it is impressive.
我不是實際跟你幹
I'm not fucking with you okay,
你知道我家入了什麼教吧
you know the church my family belongs to?
有點邪那種
It's kind of different.
他們想殺了我
Well, they just tried to sacrifice me
因為我是處男
because I'm a virgin.
什麼
What?
我之前沒做愛過
I've never had sex before.
我清楚處男長啥樣
Yeah, I know what a fucking virgin is
但你在說什麼？
but what the fuck are you talking about?
除非今晚我失身
Unless I lose my virginity tonight
否則他們會宰了我
they're going to sacrifice my ass!
獻給撒旦
To Satan!
他們在這了
They're here! Come on!
頂爆
Oh my god!
Denise，不是跟你開玩笑
Denise, it's not fucking funny!
Oh.
我要你知道是否可以
Listen, I need to know if this is going to happen
否者我要逃命了
or I've really got to run.
Neil，我不清楚你搞哪一出
Neil, I don't know what the fuck you're on
但你現在真混蛋呢
but you're being a real asshole right now.
我去開門了
I'm going to get the door.
天啊，聽我說
Oh my god, listen to me.
死了
Oh fuck.
何事
Yeah?
這很煩人
Hey, oh my god this is so annoying
但你有見過Neil嗎
but you wouldn't happen to have seen Neil?
沒
No.
我們剛才在商場玩過來
Well, we were all just hanging out at the mall you know,
聽著CD，然後他就跑了
listening to CD's  and he just ran off.
我們猜他可能發神經
We think he might be losing his mind
我們很擔心呢
we were just really worried so.
一直在胡說八道
Well, he was babbling nonsense.
這樣說，你見過他？
So, you saw him?
對
Yeah.
可以跟我們說他跑哪嗎
Do you want to maybe tell us where he went?
抱歉，你們是誰
Sorry, who are you guys?
我是Brad，要是你幫上忙
Oh hi, I'm Brad and it would be really helpful
就幫大忙了
if you could help us find him.
好的，進來
Alright, uh yeah, come in.
他們怎知道在這的
How'd they know we were here?
不清楚
I don't know.
草起了
Fucked!
草
Oh shit, shit, shit.
這褲太緊身
These pants are too tight.
好的
Okay.
噢，我的蛋蛋
Ow, my nuts!
給力點，我幫你
Come on, come on. I've got you.
快跑
Lets go.
跑
Go.
沿著這條街走
So, it's just down this street here
是單行道，所以你要經過橡樹過去
oh but it's a one way so you should just go around via Oak
而Cheryl的家應該在那
and Cheryl's house should just be right there.
你太幫忙了，謝謝
You've been incredibly helpful, thank you.
還有你們怎麼認識Neil的
Yeah, how do you guys know Neal again?
教會認識的
From church.
什麼教會
What church is that?
你沒聽過的
You've never heard of it.
我們崇拜撒旦
We worship Satan.
草
Fuck.
老兄，你什麼也沒損失
Dude, you have nothing to lose.
不，蒙羞比死更難堪
No, humiliation is worse than death.
你不會見過有傢伙
You've never walked into a room where everybody
在房間裡打飛機
has seen you wearing jizz.
我見過
Ah, yes. I have.
我做不到，我選擇死亡
I can't do it, I choose death.
不可以
No, no, no, no, no.
等一下
Wait, wait, wait okay.
你父母今晚幾乎殺了你
Your parents almost killing you tonight
可能對你說是幸事
that's the best thing that could have happened to you.
他們在你背後點一把火
They lit a fire under your ass to go out there grab
口裡說著甜言蜜語，實則蛇蠍心腸
life by the ears and make sweet sweet love to his mouth.
你是自私鬼，知道嗎
Fuck, you're a selfish prick you know that?
我怎麼自私
How am I selfish?
因為這是你最後機會，Neil
Because this is your last chance, Neil.
要是你不進去破了你處男膜
If you don't go in there and bust your hymen
那麼你就是個死人
then you're a dead man.
這一切都入了我腦
And then that's on my head
我不能這樣苟且餘生，狠狠大幹一場吧
and I can't live with that shit so fuck you.
我不想成為你人生的遺憾事
I wouldn't want me dying to be a source of guilt for you
或任何陰影
or anything.
這才是嘛
Yes!
看，沒你想像的差
Aw, see, it's not so bad huh?
草，這邊我給你來點啤酒
Uh, shit, uh lets get you a beer this way.
美女們，認識Neal嗎？
Ladies, you guys know Neal right?
Hi Neal.
Hey.
可以跟你玩一個嗎
Oh, can I play one with you?
醉了，醉了，啤酒灌倒了
Here we go, here we go, beer pong baby.
Neal,等一下
Neal, wait, Neal. Neal!
大家看，那個自摸男
Hey, look everybody it's the man himself!
我們一起來Neal
Lets all do the fucking Neal!
老兄，嗨
Dude, hey.
天啊，我所見過的其他人
Oh my god, that was the worst thing
最惡劣的一幕
I've ever seen happen to anybody.
你要來一杯
You need a shot.
為絕地翻身而碰杯
To hitting bottom.
無處可逃，唯有頂上
Nowhere to go but up.
無處可逃
Nowhere.
太難受了
Oh, oh that's awful.
誰在裡面
Who's in there?
想必是飛機男
I think it's that masturbating guy.
老兄，你在裡面打飛機嗎
Hey  man,  you  jerking  off in  there?
需要伴奏嗎，老兄
Need some rhythm bro?
一下！兩下！三下！
Stroke!  Stroke! Stroke!
Stroke, stroke, stroke!
一下！兩下！三下！
Stroke,  stroke,  stroke!
Stroke, stroke, stroke!
一下！兩下！三下！
你以為自己做什麼
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
哇
Whoa!!!
肅靜
Behold!
飛機大師
The Great Master Bater.
我史無前例露一下我的陰莖術
And I give to you my fabulous phallus of fun.
噢
Oooh!
謝謝，謝謝
Thank you, thank you.
現在我要一位志願者做下一個魔術
Now, I need a volunteer for this next trick.
你如何
How about um you.
草你
Fuck that.
沒膽鬼一個呢，童鞋們
We've got a bashful one,folks.
給他打一下氣
Lets give him some encouragement.
Kent!
Kent! Kent!
Kent! Kent.
現在，我要全場安靜
Now, I need complete silence for this next trick.
敢碰我，你死無全屍
Touch me and you're a dead man.
噢！！！
Oooh!!!!!
好的
Alright.
挑一張，任何一張
Pick a card, any card.
什麼？白癡牌技？
What? A stupid card trick?
任何牌
Any card at all.
現在讓全場看看
Now show it to the room.
都看清楚了嗎
Did you guys get a good look?
現在放回去
Now put it back.
好的
Alright.
Kent，是你那張嗎
Kent, is this your card?
草，不是
Fuck no.
這是他的牌嗎
Is this his card?
不是
No.
看一下你的褲子
Oh. Check your pants.
看什麼？
Check my what?
你褲子
Your pants.
草
Fuck!
搞什麼飛機
What the fuck!
謝謝
Thank you.
太牛逼了
That was, that was pretty awesome.
要看加場版嗎
Yeah, you want to see another one?
或許
Maybe.
草
Oh fuck.
就
Just!
喜歡我內內嗎
Like my outfit?
真精緻
It's really pretty.
承蒙
Thanks.
摸一下我膝蓋底
Take the back of the knee,right,
出奇的敏感
it's surprisingly sensitive.
不總是只有陰蒂才
It can't always be about the clitoris.
嗨，你來我教會呢
Oh hey, you go to my church.
沒錯
Oh, that's right.
見到你太開心了
It is so good to see you.
同樂同樂
It's good to see you.
Neal去哪啦
So, where's Neal?
Neal太棒棒了
Neal, Neal's amazing.
我懂的
I know, right?
他在哪
Where is he?
不，我不會告訴你
No, no, no, no, I'm not telling you.
對你而言，我不會說
You I'm not going to tell.
求你啦
Please tell me?
求求求你
Please? Please?
告訴我
Tell me?
你聞起來像肉桂
You smell like cinnamon.
好，我告訴你
Okay, okay, okay I'll tell you okay
但你來遲了，他已經在做愛了
but you're a little late because he's already having sex.
你喜歡什麼花式
So, what are you into?
除了魔術，還有電視遊戲
Besides magic I like video games,
還有火箭之類
I kind of like the retro stuff
因為很像玩遊戲
because it's more about the game play.
我是說床上
I meant like in bed.
呃
Uh.
你要幹我，要嗎
You want to fuck me, don't you?
這就幫大忙了
That would be super helpful.
是
Yeah.
我是說是的
I mean yes.
好的
Ok.
Neal?
Neal，你在上面嗎
Neal, are you up here?
你準備好嗎
Are you ready?
七七八八了
I think so.
你感覺準備好
You feel ready.
準備好
I feel ready.
不是那情況的
This is not what it looks like!
Cheryl？真的？
Cheryl? Really?
我問你先的
I asked you first.
我來只是提醒你
You know I just came to warn you that these people
你教友正趕來
from your church are coming.
我們可以繼續嗎
Oh. Can we still do this?
你開啥玩笑
You're kidding, right?
死了
Oh shit, fuck.
做點事
Do something.
太驚險了
That was close.
快跑
Lets go.
不，我在這，幫你拖延點時間
No, I'll stay here and buy you some time.
Denise，這不安全
Denise, it's not safe.
他們不抓我
They're not after me okay,
待會見，看咋樣
we'll catch up later and see what happens.
現在你信了吧
So, you believe me now?
是，我信你被撒旦邪教追捕
Yes, I believe you're being hunted by a Satanic cult.
走
Go.
見過Neal嗎
Did you see Neal?
上了個帝，派對女孩都想跟他上嗎
Jesus, is every girl at this party trying to get with him?
他在哪
Where is he?
嘿
Hi.
嗨
Hey.
Matt?
天啊，嗨
Oh my god, hey!
我想知道帥哥都跑哪了
You know, I was wondering where all the hot guys were.
你在這幹嘛
What are you doing here?
Matt，我們得跑
Matt, come on we have to go.
什麼
What?
我們得走，起來
We have to go, get up.
等一下，我牙齒貼滿嘔吐物
Wait, wait, wait, do I have puke in my teeth?
你朋友呢
Where's your friend?
誰
Who?
Neal?
你們樓上看過了嗎
Uh, did you try upstairs?
嗯
Yeah.
我要坐一下
Oh, I've just got to sit for a sec.
噢！
Oooh!!!
歐
Ow.
老兄
Dude!
鑰匙
Oh, the keys.
我們得走了
We've got to go man!
好的
Alright.
我有鑰匙
I've got the key.
你老笑容滿面
You're all smiling.
等一下，你們去哪
Hey guys, wait, where are you going?
我們不是偷車
We're not stealing a car.
是借
No, we're borrowing it.
你夠了
That's it, that's it for you.
這教會是普通型的還是?
Oh hey, so this church is it like any regular church or?
正好相反
No, it's the exact opposite.
那個祭壇處男惹毛了你們神父？
Oh okay, so your altar boys molest your priests then?
我不太清楚
I don't really know.
草，不好意思
Oh shit, sorry.
那邊
There.
最好你來，你的屎你負責
You'd better drive, you've got to be responsible here.
啊
Ahhhh!!!!!!!
不會傷害你們的
We're not going to hurt you!
跑啊
Go! Go!
出來
Get out of the goddamn car!
跑起
Go, go, go, go, go!
給力點
Come on!
你開車
Get the truck.
把她弄上車
Put her in the car!
他們怎麼找上了
How the fuck did they find us?
你那見利忘友的朋友出賣你了
I'll tell you how, your friend without benefits sold us out.
Denise?
沒門，她還幫我逃呢
No fucking way man, she helped us escape dude.
差點逃不了
Aw, barely.
你知道你說什麼嗎
You don't know what you're talking about,
你爸如何
how about your dad?
員警？
The cop?
給你五十塊，打賭他一定在你陰囊
I bet you 50 bucks he's got some
kind of tracking chip implanted
裝了跟蹤器
into your nut sack.
這鎮上到處是撒旦教信徒
Listen, there are Satanists all over this town.
可以是任何人
It could be anyone, okay?
他媽的的士司機可能是
It could be you know the fucking taxi drivers,
服務員，員警，無業流氓，他媽咖啡師
waitresses, cops, hobos,fucking baristas,
狗狗裝扮師，他媽的素食者，他媽的嬉皮士
dog groomers, fucking vegans,fucking hipsters man.
你說得對
You're right, you're right,
要多加防範
we've got to keep our eyes peeled.
底線，我們可以信的只有雙方
Bottom line, the only people we
can trust are each other, okay?
等一下，要是你撒謊呢
Wait, what if you just lied.
他們怎麼知道這些
How would they know?
他們會知道，我媽的線眼滿布
They will know, my mom is a bloodhound for bullshit.
這麼自尊心重的少年怎麼不會
What self respecting teenager doesn't know how to lie
跟他媽撒謊
to his own mother?
我一舉一動，她瞭若指掌
She can smell it on my breath.
草
Oh fuck, oh fuck, fuck.
什麼？
What?
草
Fuck!
什麼
What?
什麼事
What's wrong?
沒油
We're out of gas.
或許撒旦信徒不會這麼大膽跟到這
Maybe the Satanists will be too scared to follow us here.
先付款再加油呢
It's one of those pre-paid deals.
我來
I got it.
2號泵加50塊
Hi, fifty bucks on pump two.
為了上帝，讓不潔流出你的雙眼
Let the scales fall from your eyes
是欺世盜名，撒旦才是救世主
for  God  is  the  deceiver
and  Satan  is  the  salvation.
Sheldon跟我們說你的降生有特殊目的
Sheldon  told  us you had  a  special  purpose.
什麼
What?
我會給錢的
I'm going to pay for it.
老兄，這些什麼來的
Yo dude, what the fuck is all that?
儲糧，以便我們躲起來
Provisions, in case we have to go into hiding.
躲起來，這個
Yeah, hiding, about that.
我在想躲起來不是最好方法
I've been thinking hiding might not be the best idea,
我是說
I mean.
過來，上車
Okay, come on, get in the car.
不，這可能聽起來很荒謬
No, no, no this might sound a little fucked up
但要是這一切為真
but if any of this shit is real
讓我去死正好能拯救世界
then getting me laid might actually save the world.
上車，趕腳
Get in the car,come on.
什麼？我認真的
What? I'm kind of serious.
我知道你認真，這就是
I know you're serious,that's why this is
你太他媽瘋了
so fucking insane man.
就如“誇大妄想症”一樣
That's like delusions of grandeur much?
他們要我死
They tried to kill me.
要是這真的，沒人安全，你懂吧
If this shit is real nobody is safe, you get that right?
老兄，世界沒地獄
Dude, there is no Hell.
沒撒旦這些屎
There's no Satan or any of that shit.
你父母，我父母，Sheldon，Mary，
I mean, your parents, my parents, Sheldon, Mary,
都被洗腦成瘋瘋癲癲非正常人
they're all just brainwashed lunatics dude.
越早意識過來，你就越自由
The sooner you realize that the freer you'll be,
看我，老兄
come on dude look at me.
我活在當下，痛快自在
I'm just living in the moment having a fucking blast
不只享受一種口味牛肉幹，是兩種
enjoying not one but two flavours of beef jerky.
沒大不了，因為到我死那天
It's no big deal because I know at the end of the day
只有我自己來評斷一生
the only asshole who is judging me is me.
你知道我為何在這
You know why I'm here,right?
因為我是你唯一朋友
Because I'm your only friend.
對，因為我想分享你在第一時間
Yes, that and because I want to be there
嘗到陰道滋味後的喜悅
for the first moment that your dick tastes vaginal glory.
你想看我愛愛
You want to watch me have sex?
不是，老兄
No, no dude.
我只是想見到你開心
I just want to see you be happy.
少來
Come on, man.
開心
Be happy?
你只想間接體驗我的生活，因為你沒有
You just want to live vicariously
through me because you're not.
沒有什麼
Not what?
沒事了
Nothing.
沒關係，當我沒說過
Never mind, I didn't say that.
噢
Oh.
因為我配不上你嗎
Because I'm not cool enough for you?
因為我只是有樣學樣的朋友
Because I'm just your tag-a-long friend, right?
現在你一朝成名
And now all of a sudden that you're Mr. Popular
不能忍受跟我這樣的失敗者做朋友
you can't hang out with a loser like me?
我這樣說過嗎
Did I say that?
拜託，Neal
Oh please, Neal.
跟我做朋友
Be my friend.
這裡，給你牛肉幹
Here, take my jerky.
多少錢一晚
How much for a sleepover.
你現在要混一下嗎
You want to hang out now?
哈
Huh?
給你所有東西
Take everything.
住手
Stop.
我擁有的一切
Everything I have.
住手
Stop. Stop.
哇
Whoa.
什麼？
What?
不能想像，我會提議這個
I can't believe I'm even suggesting this.
什麼
What?
叫雞
Prostitutes.
Prostitutes!
叫雞
對啦
Fuck yeah.
Fuck yeah man.
好的
Alright.
繼續找
Keep looking.
看來情況不太妙
It does not look good I'm afraid.
他會現身的，Sheldon，信我
He'll show up Sheldon, trust me.
不必畏懼我，Gary
You don't have to fear me, Gary.
我站你那邊
I'm on your side.
但你要恐懼的，我們所有人恐懼的
But you need to fear,what we all need to fear,
是我腳下的大王
is our Lord below.
我僅僅是他狂怒的執行者
I'm merely an instrument of his wrath.
Sheldon要說的是
What Sheldon is trying to say is that -
好了,Mary
Yes, Mary.
跟他們解釋一下我的話
Explain to them what I'm trying to say.
Sheldon是說要是Neal不出現
What Sheldon is trying to say is that if Neal doesn't show up
我們要找替代祭品
we're going to need to find some kind of replacement offering.
多謝澄清
Thank you for clarifying my dear.
噢
Oh.
太傷感了
Oh, this is sad.
我們該拯救而不是剝削她們
We should be helping these women not exploiting them.
這是你的主意
Hey, hey, hey, this was this was your idea.
我只想不要像之前悲劇就好
I know I just thought it would be less tragic somehow.
停一下
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
要賺點真金白銀
Hey, you looking to make some real cash money
幫幫一對合法性欲旺盛男嗎
and get serviced by a couple of barely legal studs?
兩個都要
Both of you looking?
不是
No.
是的
Yes, yes.
多少錢
How much?
看你要什麼服務
That depends on what you want.
我只想今晚破處就夠
Uh, I just really need to lose my virginity tonight so.
嗯，我能幫你
Yeah, I can help you out.
但不是這裡
But not here.
那邊找我，叫Ashley
Meet me there and ask for Ashley.
噢
Oh.
就這裡？
Is this it?
嗯
Yeah, yeah.
有何能幫忙
Can I help you?
這是妓院嗎
Is this the house of ill repute?
不必低聲細語
You don't have to whisper.
好的
Oh, oh okay.
請上一個妓女
I'd like one prostitute please.
好的
Alright.
你們要找什麼類型呢
What were you looking for exactly?
我要好性格的
I'd like a good personality,
我要笑得甜，有胸
I'd like a cute laugh,and boobs.
他們都有胸
They all have boobs.
我們要Ashley
We'll take Ashley.
好的
Great.
嗯
Yeah.
搞定
Go with that.
好的
Great.
請坐
Have a seat.
這玩意紅眼睛的
The things have got red eyes.
你跟我來
You come with me.
你先坐著
You sit tight.
噢
Oh.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
是這樣的
See, the thing like.
你想做嗎
Do you want to do this?
想
Yes.
拜託
Please.
是的，拜託
Yes, please.
那麼他先
Then he goes first.
Well.
哇，啊
Whoa, ah.
等一下，Ashley
Wait, Ashley.
呃，寶貝
Uh, baby.
我等不及跟你翻雲覆雨
Look, I cannot wait to get with you
很榮幸你也如此
and I'm so flattered that you feel the same way
但他真該先做的
but he really should go first.
沒錯
Yeah.
我真需先做
I really need to go first.
Matt?
過來
Come on.
Matt? Matt? Matt?
搞不懂
I don't know, man.
你想玩什麼
So, what's your deal?
我想先來個手交
Well, I'm thinking I'd like to start off with a hand job
然後過渡到口交
and then you know work my way up to a blow job
再然後陰道交收尾
and then finish off with a vagina job?
行
Okay.
真的？
Yeah?
很酷呢
Uh, cool.
給我外面朋友同樣套餐吧
And the same exact same goes for my friend out there.
我要再三強調他的陰道交
I really can't stress enough how important it is
要做得到位點
that he gets a proper vagina job.
你身上有多少錢
Well, how much money do you got?
對，現金
Yes, currency.
你怎麼入行從妓的？
So, how did you get into prostituting?
我是說，你一定有些可歌可泣的故事
So, I mean you must have some wild stories.
沒什麼
Not really.
沒有？
No?
我是說至少遇到瘋狂角色
You, I mean meet any crazy characters at least or?
我想有點
I guess.
有什麼古怪花式
What's the weirdest thing
嫖妓的叫你做呢
that anyone's ever asked you to do?
有個給錢我在他狗身上拉屎
This one guy pays me to poop on his dog.
噢
Oh.
什麼狗
What kind of dog?
不太清楚，棕色毛的吧
I don't know, a brown one.
至少讓我看看你咪咪
Can I see your boobs at least?
噓
Shhhh!!!!!!!
坦白說，這是我第一次
What if I told you this is my first time?
那就拜託別哭
Please don't cry.
射了，射了，射了
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
很好
Good.
嗚呼
Wooo-hooooo!!!!!!!!!
彙報
And?
怎麼啦
So, what happened?
跟我分享一下
Talk to me buddy.
不能再快活
Oh man, was it awesome.
不只是愛愛棒棒的
Uh, I just, I mean not only was the sex amazing
我想最美好部分是
but...but you know I think that the best part was
Ashley跟我很投緣
that Ashley and I really connected you know.
真的？
Really?
嗯
Yeah.
哇
Wow.
好的
Okay.
那麼她在哪
So, where is she?
Ashley?
可憐她，有氣沒力了
Oh, uh, poor thing is exhausted.
我真的給了她，但別擔心
You know I really gave it to her in there but don't worry
我肯定她會撐得住下一個
you know I'm sure she's got another one in her
但別憤怒要是她心裡只有我
just don't be mad at me if she still has Matt on the mind.
我要做愛了
I'm going to have sex.
你要做愛了
You're going to have sex.
我不用死了
And I'm not going to die.
你不用死了，進去做吧
You're not going to die, go in there do it.
準備好了嗎
You're ready.
準備好了
I'm ready, man.
好好享受
Have a great time.
我就是個娘娘腔
I am a fucking pussy.
Ashley...
嗨，輪到我了
Hey, it's my turn.
你先坐著
You just sit there, okay.
你去哪
Hey, where are you going?
很快回來
I'll be right back.
Matt!
Neal，我們談幾句
Hey Neal, we just need to talk to you for a minute.
沒事的
Everything is okay, everything is okay
我們談幾句
we just need to talk to you for just a second.
突擊查房
This is a raid!
所有人出來
Everybody out!
Neal, Neal, Neal.
開門，員警
Open up, it's the police!
Colette，你見到他嗎
Colette, you seen him?
跑
Go, go, go!
回來
Hey, get back here!
Rod，不是Neal
Rod, it's not Neal!
Greg!
Neal!
滾回來
Get the fuck back here!
Greg!
Greg，回來這
Greg get back here!
他媽的回來
Get the fuck back here!
你個蠢貨
Oh, you goddamn idiot.
Rod，他偷了我車
Rod, he stole the car!
什麼
What?
Greg，趕上
Greg, come on!
草
Shit!
我得為你拖著他們
Well, I have to hand it to you.
你真勇回來找我
It's pretty brave of you to come back for me.
你發什麼事啦
What happened to you?
讓他們無法抽身
Just tried to keep them busy.
為你騰出時間
Tried to buy you some time,
Brad對我很和善
I did get pretty friendly with Brad.
Denise，他是敵人呢
Denise, he's the enemy.
拜託，Neal
For fucks sake, Neal.
我開玩笑
I'm joking.
你永遠無法懂，是嗎
You're never going to get it，are you?
懂什麼？
Get what?
我喜歡你，你個蠢貨
That I like you, you moron.
我也喜歡你，但你不必這玩我
I like you too but you don't have to be a bitch about it.
不是，Neal
No, Neal.
草，我愛愛你
Fuck, I like like you.
愛愛
Like like.
什麼？為何
What? Why?
我不知道，因為你像是我認識的最酷的人
I don't know, because you're
like the coolest person I've ever met?
我不酷，Denise，我都不知道酷為何物
I'm not cool Denise, I don't even know how to be cool.
真的，Neal
Exactly, Neal.
哦哇
Oh wow.
太好了，這是說現在我們可以做愛了嗎
Awesome, does that mean we get to have sex now?
不可以
No.
做愛
Make love.
你表現真的需要再好點
Okay, you really have to do better than that.
你聞起來很好
You smell nice.
不是這樣
No, Neal.
天啊，你要我說什麼
Jesus, what do you want me to say?
我一向都喜歡你，但只停留在想
That I like you but I've always liked you but I thought.
就知道你就是他媽的個膽小鬼
I knew it, you're a fucking chicken.
草
Fuck.
好的
Okay.
讓時光倒流
Lets just go back in time,
假設我有勇氣叫你出來約會
pretend I had the guts to ask you out on a real date.
約會
A date.
好的，我們去哪
Okay, where are we going?
是個驚喜，而你又同意了
It's a surprise but you say yes,
我送你回家，加送一支紅玫瑰
I pick you up at your house with one perfect red rose
我相當緊張，因為這晚
and I'm really nervous because this is the night
我要跟你訴盡一切
I'm going to tell you everything
你也緊張，因為你知道接下來是什麼
and you're really nervous too
because you know what's coming.
好的，說多點
Alright, tell me more.
先一起開卡丁車
We start with something fun like go-carting
然後去那間高級素食餐館用餐
and after we walk down to that fancy vegan restaurant.
有品味
Nice touch.
餐後到海邊漫步
After dinner we walk by the beach
然後我有了以前就該有的
and I gather every bit of courage I have
那些跟你說的勇氣
and tell you what I've always needed to.
你要說什麼
What do you say?
打從我情竇初開我就喜歡你
That I've liked you since I was old enough to like girls
但我又害怕我對你表白了
but I was terrified that if I made a move on you
我怕會破壞了友情和搞砸了
I would ruin it and screw it up
然後你不再跟我說話
and you would never talk to me again.
我的天
Oh boy.
坐穩
Hold on.
噢
Oh.
你他媽逗我，Neal？
Are you fucking kidding me, Neal?
噢
Ohhhh!!!!!!
Neal，你真他媽逗我了
Neal, are you fucking kidding me?
幹我
Oh, fuck me.
抱歉
Sorry.
天啊
Oh my god.
Neal.
給力點
Come on.
抱歉，真的抱歉
I'm sorry, I'm just really sorry.
搞砸了
It's a mess.
Denise，我真的...
Denise, I really...
搞什麼
What the?
老兄
Dude.
滲透了沒
Was there penetration?
多得不得了
A bunch.
真的？跟我說說感覺
Really, so tell me what it felt like.
就是幹的感覺
Like a fucking.
襪子套腳，正合腳的感覺
Put a sock on a foot man and it fits just right.
他還沒破處
He's still a virgin.
走
Lets go, lets go.
Lets go.
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
沒事的
It's okay.
明天打給我
Call me tomorrow.
我會的
I will.
你成功達陣了嗎
Did you, did you get it in?
你搞上她了嗎
Did you get it in her?
發生什麼事
So? What happened?
要說些話嗎
Are you going to say anything?
要跟我說說發生什麼了嗎
Are you going to tell me what happened?
好的，發生什麼事
Alright, what happened.
好的
Okay.
我跟Denise說我喜歡她
I told Denise I liked her,
她說也愛我
she said she liked me back which was great
這很好嘛，我搞到她腿上
and then I came all over her fucking leg.
開心吧
Happy?
太棒了，你本可以早幾年跟她說
That's awesome dude, shit if
you would have told her sooner
你就不必如守身如玉這麼辛苦
you could have been breaking your oath all over the place.
我們就不會淪落如此田地
We wouldn't even be here.
這樣說是我錯，Matt？
Oh, so this is my fault now Matt?
什麼
What?
不是
No.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
我只是說說
I'm just saying.
你只是說說
Oh, you're just saying.
很好，你只是說說
Good, okay good you're just saying.
我要說說的是
Ah, okay well what I'm saying
你今晚反客為主成主角了
is that you've made this whole night about you.
今晚本該是我上床的
I was the one who was supposed to get laid tonight,
你插腳進來，成全了你的破處之旅
you got in line and you were the one who had sex.
對，我跟壞妓女搞上了，行了吧
Yeah, I had sex with a dirty hoe okay,
你跟Denise那個才特別
what you have with Denise that's special,
那個才棒
that's that's nice.
草你
Fuck you, man.
草我
Fuck me?
太遲了，不再有我跟Denise故事了
It's too late, there's no more me and Denise, dude.
我回不了學校
I'm not going to school again,dude,
我死翹翹了
I'm dead like fucking dead.
死翹翹
Dead, dead, dead.
你還沒死，好不
You're not dead yet okay,
你還，我們還能逃出生天
you still，we can still get out of here
別為此怪責我
and don't blame me for this.
我怎跑，手都綁死了
How am I going to get out, my hands are fucking tied.
我手綁上了
My hands are tied!
我手也綁緊了
My hands are tied too.
你踢我？
Did you just kick me?
你他媽的踢我？
Did you just fucking kick me?
對，我他媽的踢你
Yeah I fucking kicked you.
你做什麼
What are you doing, man?
你他媽先踢我的
You fucking kicked me first.
知道你踢我很痛啊
When you kicked me it fucking hurt.
後面他媽的安靜點
Hey, shut the fuck up back there.
你給我閉嘴
No, you shut the fuck up man.
草你
Fuck you, man.
草
Fuck.
他媽想走嗎
Want to fucking go?
別
Don't even.
回來啦
Ah, there you are.
你本不該這麼多麻煩的
You are more trouble than you're worth.
而你老讓我們等
And you have kept us waiting.
我已對你再三寬容了，Neal
Well, I've got to hand it to you Neal,
而你一而再讓家族蒙羞
you continually find new ways to humiliate your family.
我蒙羞，真的，父親？
I'm the embarrassment,really Dad, me?
我蒙羞？
I'm the embarrassment?
沒錯，小鬼
Yeah, that's right buster.
這個死蠢宗教快把你腦洗沒了
This stupid religion has fucked with your heads so bad
你真的願意犧牲
you're actually willing to sacrifice
把你的親生骨肉
your own flesh and blood
給有尾巴的紅魔鬼呢
for some red guy with a tail.
哇哇哇，你頭腦不清醒
Whoa, whoa, whoa, that's where you go easy.
你崇拜一具他媽的哈佬喂服裝邪人
You worship a fucking Halloween costume.
對
Yeah.
閉嘴
Shut up.
你把媽也拖進去，看看她
You dragged Mom down with you, look at her,
她覺得你對嗎
does she look okay to you?
我不是蒙羞的人
I'm not the embarrassment.
多麼的甜言能辨
How very sweet.
是希望有更多時間做感人家庭團聚，但我們沒有
I wish we had more time for such touching
family reunions but alas we do not.
讓他們準備一下
Get them ready.
一切會好的,Neal
Everything is going to be okay,Neal.
太好了，太他媽的妙
Real nice, real fucking nice.
你親兒子？
Your own son?
你這沒膽的
You're gutless.
Neal.
振作，Neal
Come on, Neal.
別跟我說話
Don't talk to me.
我哭
I cried.
什麼
What?
我哭了
I cried.
你要說什麼
What are you saying?
你哭個屁啊
What do you mean you cried?
你想說什麼
What are you talking about?
今晚我被妓女破處失身，傷感的淚
I lost my virginity to a prostitute tonight and I cried.
對，沒錯
Yeah, alright.
都不知道怎發生的，就這樣失身了
I don't know what happened man, I just lost it.
我搞上了，但我不清楚
I mean, I had it but then I don't know
有東西夾住，然後就失了
something just snapped and I just.
至少你不會到了她腿
Well, at least you didn't come on her leg.
在右腿上？
Right on the leg?
腿上，座椅上
The leg, the seat.
太他媽難看
It's fucking embarrassing.
過來，過來
Come here man, come here.
對不起，老兄
I'm sorry dude,I'm sorry man.
過來，過來
Come here, come here man.
抱歉，這晚真的太糟糕了
I'm sorry man, this whole night has been so fucked up dude.
不
No, no, no.
是美好的
This is nice.
我要這個
I needed this.
就這樣
Well, this is it buddy.
等一下，還有另外的方法逃脫
Wait, there still might be a way out of this.
沒了
No, there isn't.
不，停
No, no, no, stop.
別平靜接受這一切
Just stop being so at peace with everything okay
聽我說，聽我說
just listen to me here, hear me out okay
我不會放棄你的
I'm not going to give up on you.
男人怎樣算是破處？
When does a guys virginity really end, right?
當他勃起的陰莖穿透物體
It's when he penetrates something with his erect penis.
對
Right.
誰說一定要陰道
Who says it has to be a vagina.
天啊，不
Oh god no.
別，跟你說這會幫你逃命
No, no, no, I'm telling you dude
if it's going to save your life
你得幹我
you've got to do me.
我不能
I can't, I can't.
你得
You have to.
你是說你不能幹你好友
Are you saying that you couldn't fuck your best friend
救自己一命嗎
to save your own life?
你要這樣說嘛
Is that what you're saying?
我不肯定“裝備”匹配
I'm just not sure the equipment would work.
太傷人的話了，我至少是8尺寸的
Be totally mean right now okay, just, I'm at least an 8.
即使你的是10
Even if you were a 10.
我只是說有多難呢
I'm just saying how hard could it be?
給我喘口氣
Give me a sec.
好的，集中
Okay, yeah, just think.
好的，我試一下
Okay, I'll try.
什麼？
What?
真的嗎？
I mean, really?
對
Yeah.
好的
Okay, yeah.
我想好好活
I mean, I want to live right.
我要你活呢
Yeah, I want you to live man.
哇哇，你幹嘛
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
那是什麼
What was that?
抱歉，我想或許
Sorry, I thought maybe.
沒前戲了，沒時間了
No extras man, no time.
沒時間前戲
No time for extras.
儘管，儘管上就好
Lets just, we've just got to go.
我們怎開始
How do we start?
呃，過來
Uh, uh, come here.
好的，你懂的
Just, just alright, you know.
草，天啊
Oh fuck, oh my god.
你是我好友
You're my best friend, man, you're my best friend.
好友
Best friend.
我們要怎麼處置她
So, what are we going to do with her?
你在這，看著她
You stay here and watch her.
不，我要看祭典呢
But no, I want to watch the sacrifice you said that.
夠了，Bradley
That's enough Bradley.
天啊
Oh my god.
她當你小孩一樣說話
She talks to you like you're a child.
我不准給你說話了
I am not allowed to talk to you anymore.
少來，Brad
Come on Brad.
你聰明，性感
You're this smart, sexy guy
手臂粗壯，胸肌發達
and with your arms and abs, this chest
是女孩都想跟你搭嘴
I mean girls must be hitting on you all the time.
在這教會還真難找單身女人
It is hard to find single women in this church.
單身女人怎樣可以成為
Well, as a single woman how would I go about becoming
教會成員
part of the church?
你得宣誓放棄上帝，搞個紋身
You've got to renounce God,get a tattoo,
對著聖經唾駡
take a whiz on a bible.
就這一切
It's a whole thing.
要是你想去看
You know, if you really want to go out there
你去就好了
you should just go.
我想，但我得在這
Yeah, I know I just can't because I have to stay here
看著你
and babysit you.
我想我沒事
I think I'll be fine.
你後面搞什麼飛機
What's going on back there?
硬不起來
I'm not hard.
恕我無能，我不會幫你吹的
Well, I'm sorry I'm not going to blow you dude.
我沒叫你吹，Matt
I didn't ask you to blow me,Matt.
我懂的，只管放進去就好
I know, it's just just get it in you know.
天啊
Oh god.
我們只是，Hi，父親
Oh shit, we were just, hi, hi Dad.
好了，分開
Alright, break it up.
時間到
It's time.
嗨，不會有評斷的
Hey, there's no judgement.
我幹了一個妓女
I fucked a lady prostitute.
一個很火辣的妓女
A lady prostitute and she was hot.
就幾小時前，很辣那種
Few hours ago, real hot.
你要抓他，得過我這關
Like, you want to get to him you got to go through me.
好的
Oh, alright.
哇，Neal
Whoa, Neal.
會沒事的
It's all good, man.
Neal. Neal.
我在這，在你旁邊
I'm right here man, I'm right beside you.
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas,
In Nomina Satanas...
撒旦王在下
撒旦大王
Satanas Rex.
呼召此名號，懇請法力來殿
I invoke his power by these names.
Belial, Baphomet, Beelzebub, Lucifer,
惡怪
Awful Monster.
跳過念名字
Skip the names.
你說什麼？
What are you talking about?
我們不能跳過念名
We can't skip the names.
快日出了
It's almost sunrise.
我知道時辰
I know what time it is,
我戴表了
I've got a bloody watch you know.
那麼你知道是時候繼續下去
Then you know it's time to get on with it.
要是你做得更好，為何不不來搞
If you can do better why don't you do it then,
接下去拿刀
go on take the knife.
不不不
No, no, no.
拿法典，拿衣袍
Take the book, take my robe,
很抱歉中斷了
I'm so sorry for this interruption.
拜你媽托，沒人關心這些名的
No one cares about the names for fuck sake.
好的，好的
Alright, alright.
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas...
大王，我們呈上這具處男肉身給你
Lord, we offer this virgin flesh unto you
你就可以從無辜的肉身上吸食能量
that you may draw strength from the blood of innocence.
為地獄國帶來永光
For the glory of your kingdom.
抱歉，Neal
I'm sorry, Neal.
撒旦王之下
In Nomina Sat
煉獄之火已到
Hells own inferno has come!
我看到火焰中他的真像
I see his face in the flames!
撒旦王在下
In Nomina Satanas.
Gary!
嘔，撒旦燒我手了
Ow, ow, Satan burned my hand!
不，幕簾起火了
No, the curtains are on fire.
我的手，他媽的燙手
Ow my hand, it's fucking hot!
孩子們
Children!
退後，退後
Back, back!
退後
Back!
不
No!
大功告成！
Yeah!
我愛你
Aw, I love you man!
好，這是你的牌嗎
Alright, is this your card?
不是
No.
現在要看我胸罩嗎
Do I check my bra now?
我幫你看
Well, I could check for you.
什麼
What?
天啊，太棒了
Oh my god, that's amazing.
這會讓你成為最強遊戲玩家
It will make you an all powerful video game god.
我上網找了幾個月了
I've been looking for this  online for like months.
你怎麼找到的
How did you find it?
生日派對客戶搞這個的
One of my birthday party clients hooked it up,
我為她5歲女兒加演一小時
I did an extra hour for his 5 year old.
太棒了
Aw, awesome.
嗯，魔力所在
Yeah, magic.
你錯過了最精彩的佈道
You missed a wonderful service.
我們很好，媽
We're good, mom.
寶貝，記住耶穌愛你
Honey, just remember Jesus loves you.
他因你的罪而死的
He died for your sins.
給我鑰匙
Give me the keys.
我要開車
I'm going to drive.
Matt?
夥伴，Shelly風采如常
Guys, oh Shelly looking beautiful as always.
你真會說話，Matt
Oh, you're so sweet Matt.
或許去吃素菜
Maybe going to grab some vegan,
開開卡丁車
hit the go-cart track.
酷，酷
Cool, cool.
我是說你也來
I mean, I'd tell you to come along.
不必了
No, no, no, no.
我很好，我要學習聖經
I'm fine, I've got my Bible study,
回頭見
catch you guys later.
好的
Alright.
你吃這全部
Is that all you ate?
你吃了整個薄餅，太瘋狂
You had one crepe,you're ridiculous.
瘋狂
Ridiculous.
可以調到基督搖滾台嗎？
Could you put on that Christian rock station?
當然
Sure.